Adrian Velazquez

Frontend Engineer | Javascript Animator | Banner Developer

New York, NY 10801 (727) 480-3173 - mobile hire.adrianV@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I'm a front end javascript digital animator and web developer with 4 years of professional experience working in large media agencies and development departments. My proficiencies lay in front end, core technologies and the development of banner ads, javascript animations, single page apps, sites and ecommerce platforms using Wordpress. **Currently building React.js Apps.**

WORK HISTORY

Bannerboy Corporation, New York, NY — Mid Level, Creative Developer, May 2018 - June 2019

Designed and developed ad banners within industry and google's double click standards. Initiated polite load scripts, studio enablers in accordance with ad serving metrics and guidelines. Developed with best practices and principles using html5, css3, javaScript es6, greensock.js and object oriented programming. Designed and optimized assets using the Adobe Creative Suite.

Elizabeth Arden, New York, NY — Digital Media and Banner Developer, February 2018 - April 2018

Droga5, New York, NY — Junior, Interactive Web Developer, April 2015 - May 2017

EDUCATION

University Of Rhode Island, RI – *Certification in Print Media and Web Development*, January 2011 - June 2011

Full Sail University, FL - B.S. in Graphic Design and Web Development, August 2012 - February 2015

Full Sail University, FL - M.S. in Business Innovation and Entrepreneurship, August 2017 - August 2018

STACK

html5, css3, javascript ES6, json, ajax, jQuery, greensock.js, react.js, node.js, npm, wordpress, rest api

SKILLS

sftp, git, terminal cli, .js
animation, adobe, dom
traversing, asset
optimization, psd to html5,
chrome devtools, atom.io,
mac os x, banner dev and
design, polite load scripting,
ecommerce, double click
studios, affiliate marketing,
jira, oop, prototyping,
marketing, business finance,
product development,
business and market research

PROFILES

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/avelazquez585/

BANNER PROJECTS:

https://hireadrianv.wixsite.co m/adrianvelazquez

REACT APPS:

- -https://bit.ly/2LK9AGM
- -https://bit.ly/2S7pn3G
- -https://bit.ly/2YOCids